Thank you for watching!
Thanks for watching.
Hello! Ste, this time with Utano Satoyoshi of Beyonds and Seasonings and
and Roko Tsutsui from Ocha Norma!
We will be bringing you this time with these two, so please stay with us until the end!
Well, as you know, BEYONDS will be releasing its 5th single next week on May 29th!
Congratulations!
It will be an AAA single called “HIGH TO DIAMOND GO CITY GO HOOK'S LAW”.
We performed “High to Diamond” for the first time at Hina Fest.
It's a funk number that is the Halopro, the BEYONDS. The lyrics are really nice and it makes me feel like I'm being pushed back.
The lyrics are really wonderful, and it's a bright and cheerful number that pushes you to run together with them.
It's a bright and cheerful number.
And “Go City Go” is a song that is very spring-like.
But it has a freshness and a feeling that BEYONDS has never had before.
It has a freshness and cuteness that BEYONDS has never had before.
It's the kind of song that makes people want to travel with you while listening to it.
Lastly, “Hook's Law”.
Mio Hirae's long speech comes in from the introduction.
It's the BEYONDS!
It's a very fun song for those who love the strong flavor of BEYONDS.
It's a very fun song and the dance moves are very easy to imitate.
The dance moves are very easy to imitate.
There are many places to store, so please pay attention!
Yes, and Tea Horse is currently on the 2024 Live Tour!
We are currently on a live tour called “Our hometown is Japan!
This tour is a live house tour that goes around 47 prefectures in Japan.
We are currently on a little bit of a tour.
This tour is a new aspect of Ocha Norma, or rather, a new side of Ocha Norma.
We are playing some cover songs as well.
There are some songs that Ocha Norma has never played before.
There are a few songs that Tea Horse has never played before.
There are a few cover songs that are a new aspect of Ocha Norma.
There are a few songs that we have never played before.
I think this is a new aspect of Ocha Norma that we can share with you all.
Yes, there will be a lot of activities this spring for both Ocha Norma and BEYOND, so please pay attention to them!
Please take a look at this video.
Here you go. Here you go.
Come on, he'll see you coming, and he'll take your leg.
Please don't give it back to me.
“Do you like this?” “Do you like this?” You sound impatient.
Don't hug me. You almost answered me. You're a cheater.
But I get it. I'd be lying if I didn't hurt you.
I'd rather just see you now
Don't be the first, I won't say goodbye
I'll pound on the window instead of being selfish
Sears are so fierce, they hold your feet back
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I want to touch you more, even if it's just one at a time
I want to touch you more I'm not enough
Let me see it, in your name
I stopped asking myself what's right long ago
I've stopped asking myself what's right and what's wrong
I feel sorry for you.
I keep worrying about my phone.
I know again. I know the same pain.
I've changed it as much as I've received it.
I'm happy.
But I can't believe I love you so much.
But it's so empty, it's so empty, it's so empty, it's so weak.
I have to go, but someone's waiting for me.
I heard there's a meaning to all this sadness.
But what good is an ending like this? What good is the sadness?
I don't know what to do with it
I want to be thought of by the one I think of
Stare at me just a little longer
Until the rain stops
Now the turbulence is so fierce, I'll hold your feet back
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
Even if it's just one by one I cry anguishedly
I wouldn't be me if I didn't touch you more
Watch your destiny
There's not a face to think of
Will you let my eyes fall away?
We're in this togetherLet's work together.
Utano Satoyoshi of BEYONDS & Seasonings and
Ocha Norma Roko Tsutsui of Haloste.
I'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much, just answer them quickly and at a good pace.
Okay, are you ready?
I'm ready.
Okay, let's go.
My motto is “If you think you've had the most fun in the world, you've won.
Tell us about a moment in your private life recently when you felt like a winner.
Yes, when I got new goods of my favorite anime.
Rocco's first triumphant return live performance next month
How did you feel when you were chosen to perform in your hometown?
Yay!
What do you take with you on tour?
Earphones.
Where is the most impressive place you have visited on tour?
Osaka.
Tsukiroko 16 years old
What are you working hardest on now?
To have no regrets.
Thank you very much.
Yes, my first triumphant live performance.
That's right.
So you're open.
Yes, sir.
Yes, it is.
I'm so happy for you.
It makes me happy.
I'm from Saga Prefecture.
I'm from Saga Prefecture, but it's not often that I get to do live shows in Saga Prefecture.
So I'm really happy to finally be able to do it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Is there a place that has impressed you so far on the tour?
Yes.
Yes, it was. Yes, I am.
I'm in Osaka Prefecture.
When we went there for the second tour
It was the last show of the second tour.
This is where
The call ban was lifted.
I see.
Even so, your enthusiasm and our energy
and our energy mixed together to create a great sense of unity.
That's why I chose this show.
That makes you happy, doesn't it?
Yes, I am.
You could hear us.
Yes, I did.
Then, please let us hear your voice a lot in the future triumphant concerts.
Yes, ma'am.
Questions for Ms. Sato after the VTR
Halostei
Demptation. Love & Joy for the forecast.
Come on, change it up
Take away the steering wheel Sleepy Ricordion
Tokyo Brown Now On the Side
Go city, go city, go city, go city, go city
Go city, go city, go city, go city, go city, go city
go city go city go city go
beyond go city go
May 29 Onside
HELLO! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask Satoyoshi-san a question.
Yes, are you ready?
Yes, I am OK.
Hello! Chotto No.1, an irregular corner of “Halo!
Satoyoshi-san was chosen as the member who wants to see what's in her make-up bag.
What is the key point of today's makeup?
Cherry blossom colored eye shadow.
Which city would you like to visit for your new song “Go City Go”? Which city would you like to visit for your new song “Go City Go”?
Mishima
Is there anything you consciously worked on for the performance of the U single?
Facial expressions for the music video
What do you pay attention to when you dance?
Silhouette
What is the best word for BEYONDS now?
Shine on, BEYONDS!
Thank you very much.
That you were chosen as No. 1 in the “Amazing Chotto No. 1”.
I'm so happy Thank you
Cherry blossom-colored performance
Yes, there were many pink and cherry blossom color cosmetics this spring.
I feel better when I use pink.
I decided to use pink around the eyes.
So I decided to use pink around the eyes.
Do you have any particular taste?
Recently, I draw my lower eyelashes.
I draw them.
I draw my lower eyelashes because it makes my eyeshadow look better.
I'd like to try it.
And one more word that is perfect for today's Beyoncé.
Shine on, BEYONDS!
Yes, shiny BEYONDS!
This is what we use when we get comments on our new songs on social networking sites, and we also use the hashtag “shiny byo-chan”.
You can also use the hashtag “shining beyo-chan” when you comment on our new songs on social networking sites.
Yes.
That's what I've been telling people.
I took this from the lyrics of “High to Diamond”.
BEYONDS, I want to shine brightly this spring.
Please pay attention.
Yes, ma'am.
We will continue after this show.
Next time
I'm Kimiyami Natsuyaki.
I'm Homare Okamura from Morning Musume。 24.
I will continue to do my best this time.
What would you like to make this time? What would you like to make this time?
Yes, Teriyaki Burger
Teriyaki Burger.
Have you ever cooked anything before, Homare?
No, I really don't usually.
I just fry an egg and sausage for breakfast.
This way, this way, this way... It's like a catch-all.
That's why it's sliced.
Maybe even a little thicker.
What would you like to start with this time?
Yes, I'd like to finish the onions first.
I just sprinkled some salt on them.
I just sprinkled some salt on them, but they're getting quite moist, aren't they?
In the microwave again...
One minute.
Morning's live concert at Budokan is coming up soon,
I'm sure you've done Budokan a few times, but how do you feel about it?
How are you feeling?
I get nervous every time,
I get nervous every time, and even at the Budokan, there are always new parts to sing, and the parts I sing are always different and increasing,
I can't relax even for a moment,
I still think about what if I skip a part in the song.
But more than that, there are the juniors,
For example, for the 17th term members, it was their first time to perform on a big stage,
They have been on bigger stages,
I think they will be nervous,
If there is anything I can do to give them advice, I will,
I would like to give them any advice I can, and I would also like to do my best so that I can give my maximum performance.
Can you see how much my condition has changed?
From the beginning.
Yes, it has.
Is it softer?
It is soft.
It's almost cooked.
Already cooked.
I like to brown onions for hamburgers if possible.
Yes, of course.
They are burnt. It's burnt.
Yes.
That's good.
It's good.
It's delicious.
If you don't go gently, it will fall apart.
It falls apart.
Yeah.
Wow.
Looks delicious.
From the top.
Here it is.
Squeeze.
Just a little bit.
The reason for pressing down like this,
If you don't burn it, it will float and the color won't come out beautifully.
Heh.
To make it even.
That's right.
Press it down.
Yes.
Uh.
Ah.
But it's getting nice and colorful.
I could check.
Checked.
Shall we return it now?
Yes, it's a little difficult.
It's a little difficult.
But, but...
A little squeaky.
Yes, that's right.
A little bit of this too.
A little squeak.Squeaky.
Yes, sir.
Ah.
But very nice.
Very nice.
Beautifully.
It's already on fire.
So the process is more like charring, coloring, and charring barbecue?
Yes, it's good.
It's good.
That's good.
Okay, let's see here.
Okay.
Then, you know, meat. Yes. Yes. That's right. I didn't cook it. Meat.
Wow, looks delicious. Yes, it is. But after all, it's going to shrink from being so big. Yes, it will shrink.
And it will be taller, too. Yes, yes.
If I had made it round like a normal hamburger, it would probably be like this now. Maybe. That's right.
It's amazing when you pile them up, isn't it? Yes, it is. Yes, it is. It's not so bad even with this. The volume. Hey...
Ah, it's still good.
Is it burnt?
I think it's a little burnt.
I'll give it back to you.
Here you go.
Wow, it's really good.
Looks delicious.
It's perfect.
Wow.
Only this one is a little bit the other way around.
It looks like a cookie.
Looks delicious.
Turn it the other way, and then slowly turn the heat down to low. Can you see the juices coming out of the meat? It's cooked through, so it's time to let it go.
Let's release them here. It might be stuck to the meat, so slowly scrape it off from the bottom and put it here. Looks delicious.
Now, here is the key to Miyabi-vinegar. The residual heat will heat it up. If you can't do it like this, you can cover it with aluminum foil or something.
Take away this oil. Mirin is 1 tablespoon. Turn on the fire and keep the heat low at first.
There are some tasty chunks of meat around, so you can scrape them up a little bit.
Yes, I'll do that. Be careful.
Yes. Be careful. Yes. Be careful.
Yes, sir. Be careful.
Yes. Be careful.
When you think you've almost got it, put a little bit of sorry out here, and there is a lot of alcohol in it.
So, since the amount of alcohol is very small, I don't use fire anymore.
This is what makes it shine.
Oh, it smells great. How is it?
Yes, I felt alcohol. But if you felt the alcohol, it's already gone, so you're good to go.
And here.
Here, please mix on very low heat.
Yes.
Now that the sugar has dissolved and the flavor of the meat and mirin have boiled down, this will be the teriyaki sauce.
Wow, it looks delicious.
I'll put it back here as it simmers.
Smells good.
Yes, it smells good.
Then, gently turn it over.
Yes.
Wow, it looks delicious.
Is it teriyaki?
It is.
Yes, it is.
Looks delicious.
It looks good.
So now it's easy to prepare, right?
Yes.
Now, just heat up the inside.
Toaster takes a long time, and the top can be fluffed up, but if you fry it in a frying pan, the sesame seeds will probably burn.
So, I think we're good to go now.
Then, it's okay now, isn't it?
Yes.
Now, while it's still warm, put the cheese on top of the top, so that it becomes a little bit sticky.
It's very American. It's good, isn't it?
First, put a thin layer of the mustard butter on the bun. Yes, how much?
You can spread it pretty evenly.
And be sure to spread it all over. Yes, all over.
Then, there are various theories about the order of spreading.There are many theories as to the order.
But I think it's fine to leave it to me. I'll leave it up to you.
Like the order of layering. Well, what should I do?
Well, let's start this way. This one first.
Poof. Yes.
Oh, but it's the perfect size. Oh, wow.
And lettuce. Lettuce.
And tomato. Tomatoes.
Oh, and then, and then again, this looks badass. Another patty.
Oh, onions later? Yes, last. Last, because it's abahanir.
Oh, wait, oh, I see. I don't know. Onions are good, aren't they? Yes, it is.
Beautiful. I mean, it's really nice. It looks great.
Hehe, I wonder if it will fall apart.
No, it's surprisingly good. Wow.
So, I spread the avocado out a bit and put it on the fire,
Oh, wow. And then I put this in,
And then I put this in, and then I put this in, and then I put this in. It's kind of fun.
Like this. What do you think?
Amazing. Okay, Maru-chan. Here you go.
It's done! Amazing.
The teriyaki burger is done.
How do you like it, Eine?
It's amazing. I think it has become the most shield-piled burger in my life.
Since you love meat, I think I made it thick, so please taste it.
Please taste it.
Please enjoy.
Bon appétit.
I can't eat this all at once.
My jaw might fall off.
I'll eat it. Bon appétit.
It's delicious. Your eyes are shining.
That's good.
How's the gravy?
It's really good.
I didn't add much flavor to the vegetables, but the flavor of the meat, the strong flavor of the cheese, it's delicious enough.
We had a great time cooking this time. Please come again.
Thank you very much.
We look forward to seeing you again. We are waiting for you.
So, that's all for now, Hello Kitchen.
Goodbye.
Good-bye.
Yes, I have a question for you, Rocco.
Yes, that's right. I'm addicted to making bread, and I'm also making a recipe that Danbaralulu taught me,
It's called “salted bread,” and I make it with a little salt. When I give it to the members, they eat it with delight, saying how delicious it is,
When I give it to the members, they eat it with pleasure, so I make it to see their smiles. I want to see their smiles. I want to eat it too.
I see. If you have a chance.
By all means.
Do you have any specialties when it comes to baking?
Yes, I am very particular about kneading the dough.
The dough is made of various flours and other ingredients, so I knead it a lot to make sure it is evenly mixed and tastes good no matter where you eat it.
Satoshi, do you have any specialties?
I often make scones to share with my family,
Recently, I have been given some delicious fermented butter, and when I make scones with it, they are really delicious.
So I put fermented butter in my scones. It's one of the things you are particular about.
Yes, it is.
Yes, it's good.
Thank you for watching.
The colors of our dreams are a little different from each other.
Still, when we walk next to each other, we feel the same heat.
Each road has its own story
Let me hear it, the future is at your feet.
It's a signal that we can do it, congratulations and assurances
I don't need it, I don't need anything
Confidence comes later, people joke around
Go ahead and humiliate yourself
What's wrong with now?
The wind's rushing me on
Youth is always a little short
There's no time for hesitation
It's got to be you
I'm sure I can feel it
I can't let you go.I can't let you get away with this.
I want to make a real move.
It has to be now.
You've been able to do this for almost as long as I have.
That's a real gift.
You're right about time, and you're right about today.
You don't teach it, but it's true.
It's always a sensory vibe.
A vibe that transcends words.
Are you ready to jump?
So sweet one, right here, jump in
I don't know when I'll be back
I don't care about the city
That's fine.
My tears.
Tears
All the smiles.
All of them
I'll carry them with me
It has to be now
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
A tailwind is rushing me
Youth is a time that's always a little slow
You don't cry when you're in a daze
Yesterday, when I was so longing to cry
I know what it feels like
A bond you can believe in stronger than a promise
Subtitle: Kiminomiya
It's got to be now, it's got to be like this, it's got to be like this
I can't wait to see how long it'll take me to get away from the glory
It's got to be you, it's got to be you I can feel it
One chance I can't pass up, more people than one, the moon filled with serious tricks
I want to see it with you now
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Hatsune Miku
Arranged by Miku Hatsune
Great work today!
Next, I'd like to show you a live video of BEYONDs new single to be released next week.
I would like to show you a live video of Hook's Law. I would like to invite you to watch a live video of Hooke's Law.
Do you know what Hooke's Law is?
I feel like I've learned it before.
This song is based on Hooke's law, which everyone has learned at least once.
It is based on the law that power is proportional to extension.
The song is based on the Hooke's law, which everyone has learned at one time or another, and it is based on the law that power is proportional to growth.
We hope that our listeners will also store up a lot of power on a daily basis
We hope this song will make you feel like you've saved up a lot of power and are ready to go out on the road.
It's a very bright pop number that will make you feel like you've saved up a lot of power and are ready to go!
There are a lot of choreographies based on springs.
I hope you enjoy it!
Here you go!
Music
In the 17th century, the English physicist Robert Wigg
discovered the following law about the force exerted when a spring is pulled with a bjorn
The following law was discovered
Force is proportional to extension
Ax section Ax section Soul over
Let's dancer bar Ha!
Axis Section Axis Section
Song Forward
Let's Dance Server
I've always wanted to protect my heart. I want to be strong.
I want to be strong
I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong I want to be strong
I can open my mouth for you
Dance, Say, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance, Dance
With you, with you, with you
♪ Pounding heart, alone, to the cheers of the crowd
Bye, Bye, Bye, Bye, Bye!
Strong power, I want to grow stronger than ever Let's go!
Be your, be your, be your, be your, be your self
I'll put all my skillful darkness on your dream heart
Kimidal power, I want to unleash Let's go!
Be your, be your, be your, be your, be your self
Banana
You'll wander and pull me into a future you don't knowI'll wander and pull you into a future you'll never know.
Shrimp Girl KX
At's Exstation At's Exstation Soul is Power
Let's dance and party
At's Ex Station At's Ex Station Soul is Power
Let's dance now
Surely we can't be strong without being weak
That's the law of the heart
The more we move forward, the more our throats overflow
To take away my self-confidence Section.
Men.
Always, always, always, surely, so many feelings
It's not perfect.
Nai nai nai, we'll stop
Let's go to the rhythm
Be your Be your Be your Be yourself
Let's go high, high, high
We'll never let go of each other's hands
And we go Yes!
Let's P.O.P.O.S. Because of the dream
Because of the tightness that always balances
Invisible power into a formula
Club in the rhythm that begins
Come on!
Every girl K.S.
Say! Every girl K.S.
Wow!
Bring it up!
I don't know how many words to say, but I want to say
Let's go! We are!
You'll be found again
One step to our strength
Power up I want to unleash Let's go
Be your, be your, be your, be your, be your self
Into a future no one knows
Everybody, I'll pull your hand Hey guys, I'm gonna pull your hand.
Epicode KX.
Axe Section Axe Section Souls Over
Let's have some fun
Exertion Exertion
That's right O-Up
Message O-Up
Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo, Bo
Force, force, pink out.
Ha!
BEYOND LIVE TOUR 2024 SPRING
The partnality's Yokohama Bay Hall concert has ended!
Thank you very much!
How was it? How was it, everyone? We could hear your voices so well today, and you always did what we have been asking you to do in this show so far, such as saying this or that, or saying how cute it is to call them this way.
I was really happy to hear that, and I think that today's concert was another one where everyone was united as one.
This tour is titled “Personality”, and I think the contents of the tour are designed to show the individuality of BEYOND as well as the charm of each member, so I was very happy to be able to show that to everyone today.
And of course, this is the first time for BEYOND to go on a live performance tour, and we are improving our singing and dancing skills.
I hope you won't miss it, and I hope your voices will also improve together with ours, so that we can deliver the kind of live performance that will unite all of us with our lovers like BEYOND.
And on June 27th, we will be performing at Toyo Spit for the final leg of our tour. This is Yumi Yamazaki's graduation performance. What is your enthusiasm for it?
Well, when this live house tour started, it was still a long way off.
I didn't really feel that it was far away, but now, I think it will be here in no time, so I want to enjoy every moment standing on the stage as BEYOND,
I'd like to spend such an enjoyable time that I can express my gratitude to everyone who has always supported me, the members, and everyone who has been cheering me on. Let's have a fun day together!
So, BEYOND and all of you will continue to make our live shows enjoyable, so please continue to support us!
That's all from BEYOND!
This is BEYONDS SEASONINGS' Utano Satoyoshi and Ocha Norma's Rocco Tsui reporting from Halo! It is time for us to say goodbye.
Here is an announcement.
BEYONDS 5th single, High to Diamond, Go City Go and Hook's Law, will be released next week.
All of the songs are very BEYONDS like, and you can see the new BEYONDS, so please check them out.
BEYONDS Live Tour 2024 spelling and personalities are now in progress.
We will visit Hokkaido next.
This is a tour where we can show you many personal parts of each member.
Please come and visit us.
And Ocha Norma Live Tour 2024, our hometown is currently being held in Japan.
Next stop is Shimane and Tottori prefectures.
This time, we will visit the hometowns of each member of Ocha Norma, so please come and visit us! If you have time, please come visit us.
Ocha Norma will appear on July 11th at AirTrip Presents and Mainichi Summer Festival 2024.
Look forward to this too!
If you have time, please come and visit us.
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more.
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time we had Satoyoshi Utano from Beyond the Seasonings and Doi Rocco from Ocha Norma.
Bye!
Thank you for watching.